Guide to the Arthur H. Landis Papers ALBA.066
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Writings, 1915-1985
  - Tales of Autumn Twilight (book): Typescripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - "Trees" (article): Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - "The Trench" (article): Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "United States of American and the Cause of the Spanish Republic" (article): Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - The Volunteer (Class of ’37) (screenplay): Correspondence and Contract, undated, May 1970-Jul 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - The Volunteer (Class of '37) (screenplay): Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - "Woodie Guthrie and the Wind Machine" (article): Published Version, undated, Apr 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - World’s End (screenplay): Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Series V: Artifacts/Memorabilia
  - Landis, Arthur: Mileage Converter, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Landis, Arthur: Soviet Medals, 1967, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Landis, Arthur: East German Medals, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fries, Alice: Shoe Taps and Banjo String, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fries, Alice: Textiles and Lock of Hair, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fries, Alice: Sheet Music, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fries, Alice: Sheet Music (large format), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)